More, more.
Let me sleep a little longer
More
I want to sleep
You can't move anymore?
I can no longer move...
Wait, wait a minute.
Ouch!
Wait, let me rest a little.
Because I feel the most comfortable when you are with me
That's why...
Ouch!
Oh no
Sorry
Ouch.
Good morning, Senpai
It's already morning
What?
How did this happen
What happened to you
What? Why did you...
Don't you remember me, Senpai?!
You really don'remember!?
That's terrible!
I'm the one that senpai hates.
The one that senpai hates is....
Sorry.
Really sorry
You're lying
It's a lie
Actually yesterday
Senpai and me
Why did my juniors Kana-chan and me?
Umm
If i remember correctly
Did you make the meeting report?
Yes, I did.
That's great!
It hasn't finished yet...
It'll be done in two days
We can do something about it
Oh no
Sorry
Yeah
My work was normal
You're so busy
Let me help
Thank you so much for helping me out at a time like this.
Don't worry about it!
Thank you very much, I have to hurry up now...
As usual she's not answering the phone....
What should we do?
What is it??
We were working on Mitsumori-yan but..
You're late!!
I'm sorry, this is Mitsumori-yan.
OK
Let me take a look at it
Onogi
How did you make these three?
Using the reference of Kato san from Zenrinshan
You're using that as your reference
Aren'they all the same?!
All of them!
Do everything over
What!?
It's not what it looks like
I'll make it again by the evening.
What's your answer?
Yes
That is no good
It was said that today at noon, but there was no time
If so
I thought it would better to keep a deadline
Feelings understand
What should we do
Let's do it.
But I'm not good at this, so...
...I'll try my best on my own!
Oh yeah?
Well then if you don't understand anything just let me know anytime
Thank you very much
Good morning
Let me see.
It doesn't break at all, does it?
Yes
Hey
What did the chief say when you showed him in the evening
He told me to redo everything and make it again by tomorrow morning
So how many pieces are there
This is my third
How many pieces
The third one out of 27?
Yes, the third one out of the twenty-seven.
Ah…
It's not funny at all!
Well then I'll do it with you
Let me see
Thank you so much
Here is a Mitsumori shot
And this Mitsumori shot
It's done, Kana-chan.
Where is she...
Excuse me!
Is it over already?!
Wow!!
Thank you so much!!!
Well well..
When you're in trouble we help each other out
If I'm in trouble please help next time
Yes
But still not sure if this will be of any help
Are you hungry, Senpai?
Yeah.
I bought some food for you if it's okay with you...
What?!
Is this really okay to give me...?
Of course!
This is a super-small room right...?
Can we just go in without permission..?
You can clean up properly when necessary
When it gets late
I often eat here alone.
Oh, really?
Thank you
Anyway it was a great help
If you were alone the course would have been until morning
That's true
It wasn't over at all
You are so kind
Thank you
Thank you for the drink.
No problem!
Shall we?
Let's have a drink
Cheers
It tastes good
Yeah, it does
Wow
You're drinking quite much
I see.
Well, since you're done with your work...
Let's have a drink!
Oh yeah
But it'll be until the last train
Okay
Thank you so much again
Cheers
As we enter this year
The amount of work is increasing
and I'm not able to do it anymore.
Did you have a hard time like that?
Yes, yes!
Even for me there were times when it was tough
But maybe just one year until we got used to each other
One year!?
It's going on for another one...
But that means you're being expected by the company, Kana-chan.
Expected? Me!? I thought they were bullying me!
Well...expected or not....
If you think about it like that then maybe we can get over this
Oh, you're so late.
Won't your boyfriend get mad at you?
Boyfriend!?
I don' have one!
Ah...I see
Sorry
You know how busy we are
There's no way he can make it
What about Senpai
Is she okay with that
Me? I'm not here either.
Really?!
You're not there...
But, you must be somewhere!
But your ideal is a bit high
Eh!? Ideal...?
No way
It's normal
Normal...?
So what kind of person is your type, senpai?
Type...
I think you have a normal type.
Well....
Personality-wise..
What kind of girl do you like then ?
Let me see
Kind
She's kind and doesn't get angry.
But I don' like to be restrained by her
Kana-chan, we're going to Shibuya in 5 minutes
Can you take a taxi?
Can you do it?
I don'think so.
What should we do now...
Should i take her home then...?
Home..?
Are you standing up already...?
No,I can not move
I can't move.
What?
Maybe,I cannot move
You cannot move
That's a problem
Well then
Shall we take some rest nearby somewhere
Sorry
Let me do that
Are you OK
Yes
This is your bed.
Kana-chan
Senpai
Why?
Let me do it
No
I'm taking your nipple
My nipple is delicious
No, no.
No...
No, I can't.
You have a big cheek!
It's okay
Let me do it
No
What are you doing?
You don' t have to go, do you
What are you doing
I can't stand it anymore, so help me.
No good
It's good, isn't it?
This side too.
Show me your hand
You're so rough
I'm just licking a little
It'so hot.
I can'take care of you anymore, Kana-chan.
Let me sleep a little longer
You can not stay like this
No...I do not have it now
Because i have
What?
I have it.
In your bag, right now
You can take it off
Use this
Yeah
Okay
It's on
Kana-chan
Are you okay with that
Let me see
Senpai
This feels so good
I can't
Here's your kimchi.
It'so good.
You feel great, don't you?
Great...
Let me hear your voice
Senpai
Oh, it's hard...
No, don't do it!
I can still sleep.
Senpai...
You're mean
Sorry
You can still do it, right?
What...?
I said you can still do it.
Come here
Kana-chan
I just said it
Because it'sensitive
Ouch!
But it'still so hard.
You can do it again, right?
Senpai
Can I do that again...?
Yes you can
Then...
What?
Salt
There's a lot of salt
Put it on
I'll put it on
Oh, it feels good!
I'm feeling the senpai's warmness.
Kana-chan is amazing...
Ah more
It hurts so much
Oh, my stomach...
That was great.
It feels good!
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute!
Oh no...
It's getting really hard now
That movement
I'm going to die
Oh, no.
Did you get out?
I was ignored...
It's your second time here
You're amazing
You can still do it, right?
Please make it hard.
What's wrong with you
Please make this harder
Harder...
No no
Wait a minute
Um, I...
What is it?
Shower.
I'll go take a shower and come back later
Okabe-kun
Don't you have to do something first
Sha..
Take
Bath
And come back
Sorry
You're the one who put your hand out
Eh!
Kana-chan
No
Eh
Uh
She's not coming in
Senpai
It's coming in.
Don't leave it there!
What...what should I do?
Isn' t it cruel to leave them alone like that
No, no
I just wanted to take a shower
Let me wash you
It's okay.
Not yet?
You still have a long way to go!
It's getting harder and harder again, isn't it?
A little...
You know what, senpai
because you have a lot of me
Again!
Ouch!
You have a lot of muscles.
I want to do it again
Let's do it
Do you?
Yes
It'so hot.
I feel sick...
Are you okay?
You're right, senpai
Let me see
Oh, my God.
One more time!
Give me more...
It's not good to do this much
No problem
Give me a lot
Senpai
Please give it
I can'take it anymore
More, please.
More!
Give me more...
Please give me more....
Give me more.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't go home yet!
I'm going to wear clothes because it's cold outside
Then let me warm your body directly
Hey, your body is so warm.
Kana-chan
I don't want to go home yet
Ouch!
Ow
It's hot.
It is strange...
Wait, wait!
Look at this
You can still do it
Your body is getting warmer, right?
Wait a minute.
You're sweating again
It feels good
Are you cold?
I'll warm you up
Wow
You're so nice
Thank you
I can't do this anymore.
Please wake up!
It's warm if you do like this
Oh, it tickles
This is bad
Feels good
Oh my god!
What's wrong?
Stop, stop.
Oh no...
I'm going to throw up again
Give me a hug
Let me go!
No, no.
Please let me out of here
You're warm
It's not enough yet
What?
What are you doing, Kouta-senpai
Let's do it one more time.
Come on, let me help you up!
I'll give you a hand
Here
You're the senpai
Me?
It'so good.
Oh, yeah...
I feel great!
My back is going to hurt soon...
Ouch, it hurts
Feels so good
There
With this
It felt so good.
I want to do it, too
What?
Please sleep
You made me feel better
So now it's my turn
Do you want me
You'really a pervert, aren't you?
Kana-chan.
Again!
Hey...
What's wrong with me?!
Nothing
Just now
It hurts
I made you feel better so this is your reward
Oh it feels good
It feels good!
This feels so good
You're hitting the deep part of my body
It'still not enough.
Ah, it feels good!
Still not enough...
I feel good, too.
The tip of my hair is very hard and it feels good
It feels so good
Senpai, more.
From behind...
Give me your hand
Ah, there...
It feels good.
Ouch!
You can't stop?
Wow
Ow ow
It's okay, you can do it!
You're sweating a lot
Let me continue
Continue?
Yes
I love you.
But...
Kana, why are you doing this?
It makes me happy to be with my senpai like this
What do you mean by that
You don't know until i say it
Senpais are actually bad guys
Really
That's what
I'm happy to be hugged by Senpai.
Kana-chan!
I'm so happy.
You just wanted me to tell you that, didn't you?
So please cry more
You're not good
You can't do it
It's hot.
Hot...
I'm done!
Kono-chan
You're going to cry, Kono
Ouch
Give it to me.
You're wet again
Senpai
Yes.
Hurry up and continue!
Let me lie down on your side for a moment
I don't want to
Lie down
It's hot
Give me more.
More!
Oh no, that's too much...
Slowly
Wait, wait.
I said it was the last time!
Come on...
Senpai?
You're satisfied now aren't you
Maybe a little more
I wonder if it's okay.
No, but...
You're pretty close to me now
Are you listening?
Yes
But this side is still amazing
Why do you say that
Wait a minute
I can't do it anymore.
You still can, right?
My stamina...
Your stamina is fine for me
Really!
Why don' you listen to what others say
You look so tired.
Is it really your limit?
Limit...
I understand now
Then, let's take a break for sex
and serve you instead
What...?
You can rest
Rest...?
Wait
Don't move
What?!
Hey!
Hey, Kana-chan...
Just look at me.
No way!
I'll do it again
Have you regained your strength?
Not yet
That's no good
Wait, wait.
It's hot!
I can't stand it anymore.
Are you going to sleep?
It's not a break, is it...?
You know that...I love to talk
It's a secret.
Please eat it
I'm going to throw up.
Wait, wait...I think it'll come out!
It's coming out!!
I'm so tired.
You still have a lot of hair on your head...
Are you feeling better?
It's the limit already....
Hey, are you okay??
Senpai!?
The limit..
Senpai!!
I see.
Senpai, do you remember?
Yes...
There'still time until the check-out though
What will you be doing then
I'm going to eat it.
It'so hot.
I can't do it anymore...
It hurts!
I'm tired too.
Uh
Uhh
Uh, oh
Pfft
Fufu
It'so hot that I can't eat it.
It was really spicy
My nose is running
Can I put it in your mouth?
Are you okay?
You can do it even though you just woke up, right
Do you feel good now
Yes
I'm glad
I love sex with senpai.
It'so...
Sticky!
I love this place.
You like it too, don't you?
It feels so good!
Oh no...
Please come here.
It's hot!
I can't reach it...
Ah, it feels good
It'so good.
It feels great!
This is really nice
Oh my god
I'm getting stiff again
I love it
Keep doing that
Give me a lot of yours
You're going to wake up
It'so hot.
Even though it is morning, you are amazing!
I'm sorry for being bad at this game...
There is still time left
Not yet?
Please sleep.
It's morning already
We still have time
Don't you think it is a waste of time
I'm not done
It's hot.
I remembered last night,
Senpai?
Oh no
Come on, come on!
Senpai's hair is so hard.
It feels good
I can't stand it.
What? You're going to move like this...
Wait a minute!
But you were sleeping, senpai
Stop me
Why
Oh no.
You should feel better too
That's not good
More?
No
I'll give you more.
Wait!
Oh no, it's going to go away...
It will be gone in a second
Give me your mouth
No
I'll be back soon, so wait for me.
Nacchan...
Wait!
Oh, it'still hard.
Wait! It just hurts...
One more time?
One more time?!
Please
With this
Just one last time
Just once
Really
Yes
Let mess up your hair for the last
Give me more
Oh no!
Put it out here
Ouch!
That felt good...
Wait a minute, wait up!!
It's okay now
Yes, I'm happy with it.
Wait...
What?
There's nothing left here anymore!
Too bad for you
You wanted to do it one more time
We have to go tonight
Well
Tonight is fine
If my memory serves me right
You didn't have plans for tonight either, did you?
[created using whisperjav 0.7]